Preliminary Guide to the Africa News Service (Durham, N.C.) Leroy T. Walker Africa News Service Archive, 1952-1998 and undated (bulk 1952-1994)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- U.S. Media (Box 275)
  - Atlanta Constitution (Box 275)
  - Atlanta Voice (Box 275)
    - Editorials (Box 275)
  - Atlantic (Box 275)
  - Baltimore Sun, ed. (Box 276)
  - BBC Newsreel (Box 276)
  - Berkeley Barb (Box 276)
  - Bibliography (Box 276)
  - Bilalian News (Box 276)
  - Black Congressional Monitor (Box 276)
  - Black Enterprise (Box 276)
  - Black Entertainment Television (BET) (Box 276)
  - Black Press (Box 276)
  - Black Scholar (Box 276)
  - Book Publishers (Box 276)
  - Cable TV (Box 276)
  - Capital Cities Communications (Box 276)
  - Cartoons (Box 276)
  - CBN (Box 276)
  - CBS, thru 1982, 1983-93, (2 folders) (Box 276)
  - CNN (Box 276)
  - Center for Foreign Journalists (Box 276)
  - The Christian Century (Box 276)
  - Christian Science Monitor (Box 276)
    - Editorials, 1976-83, (3 folders) (Box 276)
  - Christianity and Crisis (Box 276)
  - Clipping Services (Box 276)
  - Combined Communication Corporation (Box 276)
  - Commenatary (Box 276)
  - Committee on the Media Integrity (Box 276)
  - Committee to Protect Journalists (Box 276)
  - Conde's Nast Traveler (Box 276)
  - The Continent (Box 276)
  - Copyright (Box 276)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting (Box 276)
  - Counter Spy (Box 276)
  - Cowles (Box 276)
  - Dollars and Sense (Box 276)
  - Ebony (Box 276)
  - Encore (Box 276)
  - Engage/Social Action (Box 276)
  - Esquire (Box 276)
  - Essence (Box 276)
  - Fairness and Accuracy in Reporting (newsletter Extra!) (Box 276)
  - Federal Communications Commission (Box 277)
  - Film (Box 277)
  - First Amendment News (Box 277)
  - Forbes (Box 277)
  - Foreign News (Box 277)
  - Free for All (Box 277)
  - The Freedom Forum (Box 277)
  - Freedom Newspapers Inc. (Box 277)
  - Gannett (Box 277)
  - General (Box 277)
  - GEO (Box 277)
  - Great Speckled Bird (Box 277)
  - Guardian (Box 277)
    - Editorials (Box 277)
  - Harpers (Box 277)
  - In These Times (Box 277)
  - Inner City Broadcasting (Box 277)
  - Interlink Press Service (Box 277)
  - International Women's Media Foundation (Box 277)
  - Internews (Box 277)
  - Journalists (Box 277)
    - Minority (Box 277)
    - National Association of Black Jounalists (Box 277)
  - Libel--copyright laws (Box 277)
  - Liberation Information Distribution Company (Box 277)
  - Lincoln Gazette (Box 277)
  - Los Angeles Herald Examiner (Box 277)
  - Los Angeles Times (Box 277)
    - Editorials, 1976-82, 1984- (2 foldersO (Box 277)
  - MacNeil/Lehrer (Box 277)
  - Magazine Publishers Association (Box 277)
  - Media Network (Box 277)
  - Metromedia (Box 277)
  - Miami Herald: Editorials (Box 277)
  - Michigan Free Press (Box 277)
  - Middle East Newsletter (Box 277)
  - Minority Periodicals (Box 277)
  - Minority Radio and TV (Box 277)
  - Mother Jones (Box 277)
  - Mutual Black Network (Box 278)
  - The Nation (Box 278)
  - National Association of Black Journalists (see Journalists) (Box 278)
  - National Alliance of Third World Journalists (Box 278)
  - National Black Network (Box 278)
  - NBC (Box 278)
  - National Geographic (Box 278)
  - National Journal (Box 278)
  - National News Council (Box 278)
  - National Newspaper Publishers Association (Box 278)
  - National Press Club (Box 278)
  - National Public Radio (Box 278)
  - National Review (Box 278)
  - The Nationalist Press (Box 278)
  - New Republic (Box 278)
  - New Times (Box 278)
  - New World Review (Box 278)
  - New York Magazine (Box 278)
  - New York Post (Box 278)
  - New York Times (Box 278)
    - Editorials, thru 1986 (Box 278)
  - The New Yorker (Box 278)
  - Newshouse (Box 278)
  - News and World Report (Box 278)
  - Newsday (Box 278)
  - Newspaper Guild (Box 278)
  - Newsletters (Box 278)
  - Newspapers (Box 278)
    - Alternative (Box 278)
  - Newsweek (Box 278)
  - Norfolk Journal and Guide (Box 278)
  - Overseas Press Club (Box 278)
  - Pacifica (Box 278)
  - Pacific News Service (Box 278)
  - Peoples Translation Service (Box 279)
  - People (Box 279)
  - Periodicals (Box 279)
  - Petroleum Intelligence Weekly (Box 279)
  - People's World (Box 279)
  - Philadelphia Bulletin (Box 279)
  - Philadelphia Daily News (Box 279)
  - Philadelphia Inquirer (Box 279)
  - Players (Box 279)
  - PBS (Box 279)
  - Public Media Center (Box 279)
  - Pulitzer Prize Winners (Box 279)
  - Radio (Box 279)
  - Readers Digest (Box 279)
  - Reuters (Box 279)
  - The Rolling Stone (Box 279)
  - Satellites (Box 279)
  - Saturday Review (Box 279)
  - Scientists Institute for Public Information (Box 279)
  - Screen Actors' Guild (Box 279)
  - Sevendays (Box 279)
  - Sin Censura (Box 279)
  - Soldier of Fortune (Box 279)
  - South Africa Now (Box 279)
  - South Eastern Black Press Institute (Box 279)
  - The Spotlight (Box 279)
  - Texas Monthly (Box 279)
  - Time (Box 279)
  - Times Mirror (Box 279)
  - Transition (Box 279)
  - Trib (Box 279)
  - Turner Broadcasting (see also CBS 1983-1986) (Box 279)
  - TV, 1974-1982 (Box 279)
  - U.P.I. (Box 279)
  - U.S.A. Today (Box 279)
  - U.S. News and Word Report (Box 279)
  - Video (Box 279)
  - Village Voice (Box 279)
  - Wall Street Journal (Box 279)
    - Editorials (Box 279)
  - Washington Inquirer (Box 279)
  - Washington Journalism Review (Box 279)
  - Washington Monthly (Box 279)
  - Washington Post (Box 280)
    - Editorials thru 1977, 1978-90, (4 folders) (Box 280)
  - Washington Star (Box 280)
    - Editorials, 1976-79 (Box 280)
  - Washington Times (Box 280)
  - Washington Watch (Box 280)
  - Western Union Telephone Company (Box 280)
  - White House (Box 280)
  - Wire Services (Box 280)
  - Worker's World (Box 280)
  - World Institute of Black Communications (Box 280)
- U.S. Military (Box 280)
  This series focuses on U. S. military concerns and strategies for parts of the world other than Africa. Among the topics are arms sales, mercenaries, NATO, and veterans.
  - Arms Sales, 1972-92, (6 folders) (Box 280)
  - Arms Systems (including stealth bomber), thru 1972, 1973-92, (2 folders) (Box 280)
  - Defense Intelligence Agency (Box 280)
  - Disarmament (Box 280)
  - Draft/Registration (Box 280)
  - Foreign Training (Box 280)
  - G.I. Newsletters (Box 281)
  - Mercenaries (Box 281)
  - Navy (Box 281)
  - Nuclear Weapons & Warfare (Box 281)
  - Organization & Budget, thru 1976, 1977-93, (5 folders) (Box 281)
  - Strategy, thru 1979, 1980-94, (3 folders) (Box 281)
    - Indian Ocean (Box 281)
    - Indochina (Box 281)
    - Iran (Box 281)
    - Latin America (Box 281)
    - L.I.C. (Box 281)
    - Middle East (Box 281)
    - NATO (Box 281)
    - Persian Gulf (Box 282)
    - Rapid Deployment Force (RDF) (Box 282)
    - USSR (Box 282)
    - Veterans (Box 282)
    - MX Missiles (Box 282)
- U.S. Politics (Box 282)
  This series provides background information about branches of government, political parties, ethnic groups (especially African-Americans), social issues and events that impact on U. S. politics. This series does not focus on Africa but does give the positions of groups and elected officials relative to general questions of foreign policy. Among the topics are the Congressional Black Caucus, presidential appointments, the Freedom of Information Act, The New Alliance Party, and the Ku Klux Klan. Policies of Presidents Carter, Reagan, Bush and Clinton can be found here as well as in the series "Persons." Related materials may also be found in the series "U.S. Foreign Policy."
  - Politics, General (Box 282)
  - Bibliography (Box 282)
  - Congress (Box 282)
    - Black Caucus, thru 1989, 1990-94, (2 folders) (Box 282)
    - House (Box 282)
    - Lobbying (Box 282)
    - Senate (Box 282)
  - Corporations (Box 282)
  - Elections (Box 282)
  - Ethnic Groups (Box 282)
    - Blacks, thru 1981, (3 folders) (Box 282)
    - Blacks, 1982-1989, (4 folders) (Box 283)
    - Blacks, Afrocentricity, Mutlicuturalism, Latinos (Box 283)
    - Native Americans (Box 283)
    - Other (Box 283)
  - Executive, thru 1975 (Box 283)
    - Carter, 1976-81 (Box 283)
    - Reagan, 1980-88, (2 folders) (Box 283)
    - Election '88 (Box 283)
    - Bush, 1989- (Box 283)
    - Appointments, Reagan and Bush (Box 283)
    - Clinton Appointments (Box 283)
    - FBI (Box 283)
  - Freedom of Information Act (Box 283)
  - Labor, Unions (Box 283)
  - Left Wing (Box 283)
    - PAC (Box 283)
  - Legal System (Box 283)
  - Parties (Box 283)
    - Citizens (Box 283)
    - Democrat (Box 283)
    - Democratic/Workers Party (Box 283)
    - Liberals (Box 283)
    - New Alliance Party (Box 283)
    - Peoples Party (Box 284)
    - Republican (Box 284)
    - Socalist (Box 284)
  - Protest and Action (Box 284)
  - Religion (Box 284)
  - Repression (Box 284)
  - Right Wing (Box 284)
    - Klan (Box 284)
    - Moral Majority (Box 284)
    - NCPAC (Box 284)
  - Ruling Class (Box 284)
  - The South (Box 284)
  - Society (Box 284)
    - Charities (Box 284)
    - General (Box 284)
    - Women (Box 284)
  - U.S. Religion (Box 284)
    - Islam (Box 284)
- North Carolina (Box 284)
  Represented here are businesses, universities, media, political and community groups in North Carolina and broad topics about the State's economy, environment, education, and politics. Most of the files reflect activities and concerns related to African issues, but sometimes the file simply provides background information. Among the groups are Carolina Population Center, Committee for a Democratic Future, Mechanics and Farmers Bank, Davidson College, and the Carolinian. There are related files in the series "U.S. Groups," "U. S. Africa Groups," and "World."
  - Culture (Box 284)
  - Economy thru 1977, 1979-87, (2 folders) (Box 284)
    - Durham - Ninth Street (Box 284)
    - Environment (Box 284)
    - Industry (Box 284)
    - Workers (Box 284)
  - Education (Box 284)
  - Foreign Relations (Box 285)
    - Africa (Box 285)
  - Groups (Box 285)
    - Afro-American Center, Duke (Box 285)
    - ALSC (Box 285)
    - NC Africanists (Box 285)
    - Carolina Population Center (Box 285)
    - Chapel Hill Peace Center (Box 285)
    - Committee for a Democratic Future, Durham (Box 285)
    - Committee for Medical Aid to Southern Africa (Box 285)
    - Communist Workers Party (Box 285)
    - Community Control Movement of the South (Box 285)
    - Community Welfare Rights Organization (Box 285)
    - Food and Hunger (Box 285)
    - Infant Formula Action Coalition (Box 285)
    - Institute for Southern Studies (Box 285)
    - Mechanics and Farmers Bank (Box 285)
    - Motsu Project (Box 285)
    - N.C. Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression (Box 285)
    - N.C. Div. of United Nations Association (Box 285)
    - NCNB Coalition (Box 285)
    - N.C. PIRG (Box 285)
    - N.C. Political Prisoners Committee (Box 285)
    - Other (Box 285)
    - Research Triangle (Box 285)
    - Research Triangle International Visitors Center (Box 285)
    - Southeast Consortium for International Development (Box 285)
    - Southeastern Dialogue (Box 285)
    - Twin Streams Educational Center (Box 285)
    - United Fund (Box 285)
    - VENCEREMOS Brigade (Box 285)
    - Vietnamese Children's Fund (Box 285)
    - War Resisters League (Box 285)
    - Witness for Peace (Box 285)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Box 285)
  - Health (Box 285)
  - Legal System (Box 285)
  - Media (Box 285)
    - Business N.C. (Box 285)
    - Carolina School of Broadcasting (Box 285)
    - Carolina Times (Box 285)
    - Carolina Times: Editorials (Box 285)
    - Carolinian (Box 285)
    - Durham Morning Herald (Box 285)
      - Editiorials (Box 285)
    - North Carolina Independent (Box 285)
    - Radio and Television (Box 285)
    - Raleigh News and Observer (Box 285)
    - WVSP (Box 285)
  - Politics thru 1983, 1984-91 (Box 286)
    - 1984 Senate Race (Box 286)
    - Ultra Right Wing (Box 286)
  - Religion (Box 286)
  - Society (Box 286)
    - Blacks (Box 286)
    - Native Americans (Box 286)
    - "Ruling Class" (Box 286)
    - Women (Box 286)
  - Universities (Box 286)
    - Davidson (Box 286)
    - Duke (Box 286)
      - thru 1981, 1982-92, (3 folders) (Box 286)
      - Nixon Library (Box 286)
      - Primate Center (Box 286)
      - Journalism Program (Box 286)
      - Symposium on "Poverty and Change in S. Africa ... " Feb 1989 (Box 286)
    - N.C. A State University (Box 286)
    - N.C. Central University (Box 286)
    - N.C. Wesleyan (Box 286)
    - UNC-Chapel Hill (Box 286)
    - UNC-Greensboro (Box 286)
    - N.C. State (Box 286)
    - Western Carolina (Box 286)
- World (Box 286)
  This series begins with a focus on broad issues that impact countries throughout the world (Box 286-310). Topics include children, commodities, finance, food, housing, migration, nuclear energy, population, tourism, trade, water, and workers. The files on commodities (e.g., cashews, gold, oil, sugar, tobacco, and uranium) include a generous amount of U. S. government reports. There are also files on international organizations (Box 305 - 306) that were involved with Africa. Files on the United Nations (Box 311-316) comprised a significant portion of this series. These files document the involvement of the UN in the formation and the economic and political development of African countries. Topics covered include aid, decolonization, education, health, and peacekeeping. There are files about various branches of the UN such as UNICEF, UNESCO, FAO, and WHO; and UN-sponsored conferences such as the Summit for the Environment, Decade for Women and International Literacy Year. This series concludes with files documenting Africa's relations with other parts of the world (Box 316-332). Topics include humanitarian aid, economic development, trade, cultural exchange and tourism. These files are organized by region or continent such as Latin America and Asia. Within each region are files for individual countries.
  - Children 1989-1995, (2 folders) (Box 286)
  - Culture (Box 286)
  - Economy (Box 287)
    - Commodities (Box 287)
      - Agriculture (Box 287)
      - Agribusiness Manual (Box 287)
      - Documents (Box 287)
      - Fertilizer (Box 287)
      - Aid, thru 1984-1996, (2 folders) (Box 287)
      - Antarctic (Box 287)
      - Bank for International Settlement (Box 287)
      - Banking - BCCI (Box 287)
      - Bibliography (Box 287)
      - Club of Rome (Box 287)
      - Commodities (Box 287)
      - Ammonia (Box 287)
      - Antimony, thru 1979, 1979-90, (4 folders) (Box 287)
      - Asbestos (Box 287)
      - Bamboo (Box 287)
      - Banana (Box 287)
      - Bauxite and Aluminum, 1970's, 1981-85, (5 folders) (Box 287)
      - Cashews (Box 288)
      - Chromium, 1981-83, 1988-90, (4 folders) (Box 288)
      - Coal (Box 288)
        - 1981-90, (4 folders) (Box 288)
        - South Africa, (5 folders) (Box 288)
        - Gasification (Box 288)
      - Cobalt (Box 288)
      - Coconut (Box 288)
      - Coffee (Box 288)
        - thru 1975, 1976-79, (6 folders) (Box 288)
        - Coffee 1980-87, (6 folders) (Box 289)
        - Coffee: U. S. (Box 289)
      - Copper 1977-92, (10 folders) (Box 289)
      - Columbium & Tantalum (Box 289)
      - Cotton, (2 folders) (Box 289)
      - Crushed Stone (Box 289)
        - Commodities (Box 289)
      - Diamonds, thru 1973, 1974-92, (6 folders) (Box 289)
      - Essential Oils (Box 290)
      - Ferroalloys (Box 290)
      - Fibers (Box 290)
      - Fish (Box 290)
      - Fluorospar (Box 290)
      - Froth Flotation (Box 290)
      - Fruit, 1988 (Box 290)
      - Gallium (Box 290)
      - Gems (Box 290)
      - Ginseng (Box 290)
      - Gold (Box 290)
        - General Reference (Box 290)
        - thru 1970 - 1980, 1989, (10 folders) (Box 290)
        - Gold, 1979-92, (6 folders) (Box 291)
      - Grains (Box 291)
      - Helium (Box 291)
      - Iodine (Box 291)
      - Industrial Minerals (Box 291)
      - Iron and Steel, pre-1977, 1977-88, (8 folders) (Box 291)
      - Jojoba (Box 291)
      - Jute (Box 291)
      - Khat (Box 291)
      - Lead (Box 291)
      - Lithium (Box 291)
      - Manganese (Box 291)
      - Marijuana (Box 291)
      - Meat 1988 (Box 291)
      - Mercury (Box 291)
      - Minerals (Box 291)
      - Molybdenum, 1983-86, 1987-88, (2 folders) (Box 291)
        - Molybdenum (Box 292)
      - Nickel, thru 1977, 1978-83, 1985, (4 folders) (Box 292)
      - Non-Ferrous Metals (Box 292)
      - Oil, 1975-82, (14 folders) (Box 292)
        - Oil (Box 293)
          - 1983-88, (5 folders) (Box 293)
        - Bibliography (Box 293)
        - Companies, thru 1977, 1978-88, (4 folders) (Box 293)
        - Exploration (Box 293)
        - LCD's (Non-OPEC) (Box 293)
        - OAPEC (Organization of Arab Petroleum Exporting Countries) (Box 293)
        - OPEC (Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries) (Box 293)
        - "Recycling" Monetary (Box 293)
        - Reference (Box 293)
        - Trilateral (Box 293)
          - General (Box 293)
          - Seeds (Box 293)
      - Palm Oil (Box 294)
      - Peanuts (Box 294)
      - Petroleum (Box 294)
      - Phosphate, 1980-83, 1987-88, general, (6 folders) (Box 294)
      - Platinum, 1977-88, (6 folders) (Box 294)
      - Rubber (Box 294)
      - Sugar, thru 1976, 1977-88, (9 folders) (Box 294)
      - Tea (Box 294)
      - Tobacco, thru 1977, 1978, 1981-84, (4 folders) (Box 294)
      - Tungsten (Box 294)
      - Uranium (Box 295)
        - 1979-1989 (Box 295)
      - Africa (Box 295)
      - Australia (Box 295)
      - Cartel, thru 1976, 1977-82, (3 folders) (Box 295)
      - Canada (Box 295)
      - Namibia (Box 295)
      - South Africa (Box 295)
      - U.S.A. (Box 295)
      - U.S.S.R. (Box 295)
      - Vanadium (Box 295)
      - Zinc (Box 295)
    - Communications (Box 295)
    - Drugs, Illegal (Box 295)
    - Energy (Box 295)
    - Energy: Alternative Energy Sources (Box 295)
    - Environment, 1972-1995, (4 folders) (Box 295)
    - Environment (Box 296)
      - Atmosphere (Box 296)
      - Biological Diversity (see also African Wildlife) (Box 296)
      - Deserts (Box 296)
      - Forests (Box 296)
      - Global Environment Facility (GEF?NEAP) (Box 296)
      - Oceans (Box 296)
      - Toxic Wastes (Box 296)
    - Finance and Investment (Box 296)
      - pre 1976, 1976-88, (4 folders) (Box 296)
      - Banks, 1979-90, (3 folders) (Box 296)
      - Banks: Reference (Box 296)
      - Debt, (2 folders) (Box 296)
      - Development 1988-1992 (Box 296)
    - Finance and Investment (Box 297)
      - Development, 1993 (Box 297)
      - Human Development (Box 297)
      - International Financial Institutions (Box 297)
      - Loans to LDC's, 1976-88, (8 folders) (Box 297)
    - Fishing (Box 297)
    - Food, thru 1973, 1974-77, (5 folders) (Box 297)
    - Food (Box 298)
      - 1978-88, (7 folders) (Box 298)
      - Bibliography (Box 298)
      - Nutrition (Box 298)
      - Nutrition: Nestle's Baby Formula, (2 folders) (Box 298)
    - General, pre 1976, 1977-79, (3 folders) (Box 298)
    - General 1980-1993, (3 folders) (Box 299)
    - Housing/ Urban Development (Box 299)
    - IBRD (World Bank), pre 1976, 1976-93, (11 folders) (Box 299)
    - IBRD (World Bank) 1994 (Box 300)
    - IBRD/IMF, 1976-93, (3 folders) (Box 300)
    - IBRD/IMF: NGOs (Box 300)
    - IMF (Box 300)
      - pre 1976, 1976-94, (10 folders) (Box 300)
      - Documents (Box 300)
      - Press Releases 1975-76 (Box 300)
      - Press Releases, 1977-88, (3 folders) (Box 301)
      - South Africa (Box 301)
        - thru 1981, 1982-84, (4 folders) (Box 301)
        - 1980 Document (Box 301)
    - Income Distribution (Box 301)
    - Industrial Development (Box 301)
    - Industries (Box 301)
      - Aircraft (Box 301)
      - Arms (Box 301)
      - Automobile (Box 301)
      - Chemicals (Box 301)
      - Computers (Box 301)
      - Electronics (Box 301)
      - Pharmaceutical (Box 301)
    - Insurance (Box 301)
    - Law of the Sea, thru 1975, 1976-86, (7 folders) (Box 301)
    - LDC's, (Lease Developed Countries) thru 1976, 1977-90, (3 folders) (Box 301)
    - Migration (Box 302)
    - Minerals: General (Box 302)
    - Monetary (Box 302)
      - 1971-91, (3 folders) (Box 302)
      - Currency Rates (Box 302)
    - N.I.E.O. (Box 302)
    - North-South, 1976-93-, (3 folders) (Box 302)
    - Nuclear Energy (Box 302)
      - Africa (Box 302)
      - Asia (Box 302)
      - Canada (Box 302)
      - Enrichment (Box 302)
      - Europe (Box 302)
      - Export Control (Box 302)
      - Japan (Box 302)
      - Mid-East (Box 302)
      - South America (Box 302)
      - U.S.S.R. (Box 302)
    - Oceans (see also Environment: Ocean) (Box 302)
    - OECD (Box 302)
    - Population, thru 1974, 1975-93, (7 folders) (Box 303)
    - Shipping (Box 303)
    - Technology, thru 1978; 1979-92, (4 folders) (Box 303)
    - Tourism (Box 303)
    - Trade, thru 1977, 1978, (2 folders) (Box 303)
    - Trade (Box 304)
      - 1979-1996, (4 folders) (Box 304)
      - G-7 (Group of 7 Nations) (Box 304)
      - TOES (The Other Economic Summit) (Box 304)
    - Transnational Corporations (Box 304)
    - Transport (Box 304)
    - Trilateral Summits, 1975-89, (2 folders) (Box 304)
    - UNCTAD (see also UN: UNCTAD) (Box 304)
      - pre 1976, 1976-81, (3 folders) (Box 304)
      - News releases - UNCTAD IV, 1976 (Box 304)
    - U.N. Special Session, 1975 (Box 304)
    - Water (Box 304)
    - Water: "Decade Watch" (Box 304)
    - Weather (Box 304)
    - Workers (Box 304)
  - Education (Box 305)
  - Africa Groups: ICSA (Box 305)
  - Groups (Box 305)
    - Afro-Asian Peoples Solidarity Organization (AAPSO) (Box 305)
    - Afro-Asian Writers Conference (Box 305)
    - Amnesty International (Box 305)
    - L'Association mondiale de prospective sociale (Box 305)
    - Association of Third World Economists (Box 305)
    - Atlantic Institute (Box 305)
    - Beijer Institutes (Box 305)
    - Bilderberg (Box 305)
    - Boy Scouts (Box 305)
    - Center for Our Common Future (Box 305)
    - Christian Peace Conference (Box 305)
    - Churches and South Africa (Box 305)
    - Coordinating Committee for International Voluntary Service (Box 305)
    - Democracy International (Box 305)
    - Ecumenical Development Cooperative Society (Box 305)
    - Elie Wiesel Foundation for Humanity (Box 305)
    - Human Rights Watch (including Helsinki Watch, etc.) (Box 305)
    - Independent Committee on International Development Issues (Box 305)
    - International Association of Democratic Jurists (Box 305)
    - International Club of Rome (Box 305)
    - International Coalition for Development Action (Box 305)
    - International Commission of Jurists (Box 305)
    - International Committee for a Community of Democracies (Box 305)
    - International Cooperation for Socio-Economic Development (Box 305)
    - International League for Human Rights (Box 305)
    - International League of Students (Box 305)
    - International Service Association (Box 305)
    - International Union of Students (Box 305)
    - International University Exchange Fund (Box 305)
    - Inter-Parliamentary Union (Box 305)
    - Interpol (Box 305)
    - Knights of Malta (Box 305)
    - List of Africa Lib. -- MVT's and Support Groups (Box 305)
    - Lutheran World Federation (Box 305)
    - Medicins Sans Frontieres (Box 305)
    - North - South Institute (Box 305)
    - Outward Bound (Box 305)
    - Red Cross (Box 305)
    - Rotary (Box 305)
    - Socialist International (Box 305)
    - Society for International Development (Box 305)
    - South Commission (Box 305)
    - Transparency International (Box 306)
    - Trilateral Commission (Box 306)
    - War Resister's League (Box 306)
    - Women's World Banking (Box 306)
    - World Campaign Against Military and Nuclear Collaborations with South Africa (Box 306)
    - World Center for Computers and Human Resources (Box 306)
    - World Council of Churches (Box 306)